Rob Letts

Senior Front End Web Developer

Email: roblettsdev@gmail.com

Phone: +447449983319 Location: London, UK GitHub: rob-letts LinkedIn: robertletts Site: robletts.dev





HTML

SVG





CSS

SCSS





JavaScript

TypeScript





Vue.js

Vite





Nuxt

Storybook





TailwindCSS

GSAP





Vitest

Cypress

Bio

Senior front end web developer based in South London specialising in modern CSS, front end performance, scalable component architectures, and design systems.

Advocate for universal accessibility and utilising platform standards to sustainably further positive web experiences.

Conscious and empathetic individual that prioritises open communication and empowering colleagues. Previous career in live events and music venue management.

Experienced with CI/CD, mentoring junior developers, WCAG compliance, rendering strategies, and optimising for core web-vitals.

Education

MSc, Computer Science - Distinction September 2020 - September 2021 Birkbeck, University of London

BA, Music and Sonic Media - 2:1 September 2010 - June 2013 Birkbeck, University of London

Employment

TixTrack - Senior Front End Engineer October 2024 - Present

TixTrack - Front End Engineer June 2022 - October 2024

International ticketing solutions for live events and museums - primarily for Broadway NYC and London's West End theatres. Primarily tasked with increasing adoption of an in-house design system across multiple front end and full-stack teams, as well as migrating and extending an existing legacy Angular architecture to Vue 3 in both admin dashboard and consumer checkout contexts.

Red Snapper - Junior Front End Web Developer October 2021 - June 2022

London-based web design and development agency offering web implementations and consultancy for a variety of clients, including the BBC and British Medical Journal.